

# MISHA KUSHKA

**Blockchain Developer** 

- 380 50 90 26 321

in lin	kedin.com/in/misha-kushka-60787312k
--------	-------------------------------------



## **CAREER SUMMARY**

I have broad experience with Blockchain technology, creating projects from scratch, writing Ethereum smart-contracts, tokens (ERC-20, ERC-721). I have created several full blockchain applications (smart contract -> web3.js -> Node.JS backed -> frontend), participated in many blockchain hackathons, won prizes on two of them. Now, after graduating from the university with a diploma with honors, I (at last) have plenty of time and ambitions to dedicate it to work. Hope to hear from you soon!

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Ethereum Blockchain Developer**

Nov 2017 - Aug 2018

Was an API developer for an Ethereum crypto wallet, did several pieces of research about new blockchains. Helped to maintain a website and Android application of a company.

#### Web Developer / Blockchain Developer

Oct 2017 - May 2018

Helped to develop a website for ICO. Developed several Ethereum ERC20 smart-contracts.

### Bitcoin Blockchain Developer

Sep 2016 - Oct 2016

Developed a product to protect ownership of any document, audio, image, etc. by utilizing blockchain technology.

## **Full Stack Developer**

Jun 2015 - Sep 2015

Developing an interactive website to help users with finding clothes. This was made by creating a customizable virtual room with clothes that the user could wear onto the mannequin.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### Leadership

I was a Team leader of the Youth Committee in the U-Report project launched by UNICEF from March 2017 to August 2017. My role was to manage the work of a committee and organize events for it. Also, as a team leader, I was presenting the U-Report project in Youth Speak Forum held in Kyiv in 2017.

#### Volunteering

Before being a team leader, I was a volunteer in one of the UNICEF projects called U-Report from May 2016 to August 2017.



Deep Learning Specialization



The Data Science Course 2020: Complete Data Science Bootcamp



Cryptography I



Machine Learning



Python for Data Science and Al

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

Bank4You

**BitRent** 

Freelance

**Family Nest** 

Python
Python
PostgreSQL
Bitcoin Blockchain
Ethereum Blockchain
Solidity
JavaScript
CSS
HTML
Others

**EDUCATION** 

Git

**Android** 

geth

Sketch

#### **BSc in Software Engineering**

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute, Kyiv Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

web3.js

iOS

C#

C++

Postman

## High School Diploma (math / physics)

The 145th Natural Science Lyceum, Kyiv Sep 2012 - May 2016

### **LANGUAGE**

English (Advanced)

Ukrainian (Native)

Russian (Native)

## **IELTS RESULTS**

Listening	7.5	Writing	6.0
Reading	8.0	Speaking	7.0
Overall	7.0	1 Aug 2019	

November 2, 2019

To Whom It May Concern:

I am pleased to recommend Mykhailo Kushka as a reliable and trustworthy blockchain developer with great potential. <u>I am a CTO at Bank4YOU Group</u>, where Mykhailo was employed as an Ethereum blockchain developer from 11/2017 to 08/2018, and I have been his supervisor during this period. All his responsibilities were connected to the blockchain technology, including Ethereum smart contracts development, backend development for the interaction with the Ethereum blockchain, and blockchain research and consulting.

Mykhailo has excellent communication skills that helped him to work closely with other developers and swiftly achieve his objectives. It was quicker for him to ask a person directly in a friendly conversation rather than communicating through the CRM system. Another essential feature of Mykhailo is his curiosity. He is not only willing to learn more about anything regarding cryptocurrencies or blockchain technology but tends to have awareness in other fields as well. It was especially noticeable when he conducted a little research for the company about a new cryptocurrency. In the survey, Mykhailo showed a comprehensive theoretical background and the utmost attention to detail.

Last summer, our team worked on the creation of an iOS application (Blockchain based Money Remittance Service) to store tokens, where Mykhailo's role was creating an API for all blockchain-based operations. He managed to develop everything precisely and in time.

His skills are not only limited to the blockchain, but he also participated in developing both frontend and backend parts of a website for selling Ethereum tokens. Moreover, Mykhailo was engaged in fixing some bugs on the website of the company and in its Android application.

I would wholeheartedly recommend Mykhailo as a blockchain developer. Please do not hesitate to contact me at <u>ro@siroccopost.com</u> or <u>r.otradny@bank4you.life</u> or <u>+380 (93) 391 91 99</u> for any further information.

Yours truly,

Roman Otradny
CTO - Bank4YOU Group
Product Manager - SiroccoPAY
ro@siroccopost.com
r.otradny@bank4you.life
+380 (93) 391 91 99